{
  "name": "Essential Spanish Vocabulary for Beginners",
  "id": "1729550475609",
  "description": "This deck contains essential Spanish vocabulary for beginners.",
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "Hola",
      "back": "Hello",
      "tags": [
        "greeting",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "¿Cómo estás?",
      "back": "How are you?",
      "tags": [
        "greeting",
        "front"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "Gracias",
      "back": "Thank you",
      "tags": [
        "politeness",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "Por favor",
      "back": "Please",
      "tags": [
        "politeness",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "Sí",
      "back": "Yes",
      "tags": [
        "affirmation",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "No",
      "back": "No",
      "tags": [
        "negation",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "¿Qué hora es?",
      "back": "What time is it?",
      "tags": [
        "front",
        "time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "Me llamo...",
      "back": "My name is...",
      "tags": [
        "introduction",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "Tengo una pregunta",
      "back": "I have a front",
      "tags": [
        "expression",
        "basic"
      ]
    },
    {
      "front": "¿Dónde está el baño?",
      "back": "Where is the bathroom?",
      "tags": [
        "front",
        "directions"
      ]
    }
  ]
}